<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[StreamerPride Network]]></title><description><![CDATA[Supporting LGBTQ+ Streamers.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:42:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Meet The New StreamerPride Members]]></title><description><![CDATA[We have exciting news! As many of you know, after launching in late May, we went on the search for new members. We spoke to over 25 amazing…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/new-members/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/new-members/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;We have exciting news!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As many of you know, after launching in late May, we went on the search for new members. We spoke to over 25 amazing streamers in the process, and ultimately selected 6 incredible people to add to our ranks, for a total of 10 StreamerPride members!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have decided to invite &lt;strong&gt;Jay&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitch.tv/jonattanjay&quot;&gt;JonattanJay&lt;/a&gt;), Will (rac_kuhns), Kyle (capnfoam), Malik (blizzb3ar), Emre (Cenric89) and Sam (chemicollins) into our midst. We are individually highlighting each of these new members on our twitter account and discord server in the lead-up to our pride month fundraiser on the 28th (more information available on twitter/discord and coming to the website soon). Check out the members page on this website to see all their profiles and find links to their individual twitch channels!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be putting out additional calls for membership applications later this year, but for now want to focus on ensuring each of these new members gets the attention and care they deserve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We wish our new members a warm welcome!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Call for Membership Applications!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello Friends! StreamerPride Network has cautiously taken its first steps the other day, and now we are looking to grow beyond our…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/membership-applications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/membership-applications/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Hello Friends!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;StreamerPride Network has cautiously taken its first steps the other day, and now we are looking to grow beyond our 5 founding members!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are an LGBTQ+ streamer looking for a welcoming community and support network in which you can make a difference, you should reach out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the spirit of diversity and to represent the entirety of the LGBTQ+ spectrum, we would like to specifically, but not exclusively, encourage trans, non-binary, and women streamers to get in contact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What Does Membership Offer You?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a member, you will be invited with open arms into a warm, positive, affirmative community of like-minded people to network with and to grow and learn together. We care strongly about mutual support and encourage that through activities such as shout-outs, collaborations, events, and using twitch features like hosting and raiding. Our network is a safe place that helps you reach your potential alongside a fantastic group of people with the same goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What Do We Expect Of Members?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for members of the LGBTQ+ community who stream actively, show potential as streamers, we feel would make a good fit for our existing members, are dedicated to issues of social justice, and are willing to put in the active work to improve their own craft, and to support the network. That means streaming regularly (we suggest with a regular schedule of at least 1-2 streams a week, but there are no hard rules) and contributing actively to the network and network events. We do not take your current following or how long you have been streaming into account – one of our core aims is to help new and small streamers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How Can You Apply?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you think joining StreamerPride Network might be right for you, DM our official @streamerpride Twitter account with a short introduction, a link to your twitch channel, and why you think you’d be a good fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We strongly suggest you join our Discord community before applying so we can get to know you, and to have an active Twitch profile we can refer to and watch some of your VODs and join some of your upcoming live streams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We aim to announce our first slate of additional members around the middle of this month, but will continue adding members at regular intervals afterward, so if you do not get chosen, or your application came in a bit late, we will consider you for future slates.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meet StreamerPride Network!]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s been a long journey, but here we are. Today, we proudly announce StreamerPride Network! This all-new LGBT+ streamer group is our baby…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/meet-spn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/meet-spn/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;It’s been a long journey, but here we are. Today, we proudly announce StreamerPride Network!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This all-new LGBT+ streamer group is our baby, and we have big plans for it. We are today launching with a core group of &lt;a href=&quot;/StreamerPride/members&quot;&gt;5 founding members&lt;/a&gt;, but are already on the hunt for and in preliminary talks with potential future members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aim of our network is simple:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;StreamerPride.Network is a group of LGBTQ+ streamers from around the world. We aim to create a safe, welcoming, and supportive environment where we learn, grow, and connect. We stand together in pride and welcome all parts of the rainbow. We provide a network of mutual support and bring opportunities for growth, learning, and friendship to new and established streamers alike.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going forward, we will exist as a support network for LGBTQ+ streamers to safely collaborate and find community, and will begin providing resources for streamers as well as planning network events such as fundraisers for relevant charities. Stay tuned for more information on here and through our social media profiles soon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to be part of this new, exciting endevour with us, you can join the official StreamerPride Discord server, and if you think you might be a good fit as a member of the Network itself, you may find more info here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our first event is a celebratory 10 hour series of live streams showcasing all our founding members one by one, to be held TOMORROW, Saturday, May 30, at 10:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10AM – 12PM: CaptainFel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12PM – 2PM: KayteeKhaos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2PM – 4PM: WillFletchUK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4PM – 6PM:  jygglypuffdaddy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6PM – 8PM: hutchinsane_&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These streams will happen on each streamer’s personal twitch profiles, refer to the timetable above for more details, and will lead directly into each other. Each streamer will be giving you a hint of what you can usually expect on their channels – a great way to meet our founders!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We hope to take you along on this journey with us. Let’s support each other, and thrive together as the beautiful rainbow we are!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We Are Looking For Members!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Now that StreamerPride Network has taken its first public steps, we are looking for our first slate of members! As a network meant to…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/looking-for-members/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/looking-for-members/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Now that StreamerPride Network has taken its first public steps, we are looking for our first slate of members!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a network meant to support and uplift LGBT+ streamers from around the world, we are constantly looking for more LGBT+ siblings, from big to small, new to experienced, to join our ranks. Currently, StreamerPride Network consists of its &lt;a href=&quot;/StreamerPride/members&quot;&gt;5 founders&lt;/a&gt;, and we aim to reveal our first line-up of new members around the middle of the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What Does Membership Offer You?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a member, you will be invited with open arms into a warm, positive, affirmative community of like-minded people to network with and to grow and learn together. We care strongly about mutual support and encourage that through activities such as shout-outs, collaborations, events, and using twitch features like hosting and raiding. Our network is a safe place that helps you reach your potential alongside a fantastic group of people with the same goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What Do We Expect Of Members?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In potential members we look for people who are part of the LGBT+ community, show potential as streamers, we feel would fit into our existing community well, are willing to put in both the work to improve their own craft, and to support each other and the network. That means streaming regularly (we suggest with a regular schedule of at least 1-2 streams a week, but there are no hard rules) and contributing actively to the network and network events. We do not take your current following into account – one of our core aims is to help new and small streamers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How Can You Apply?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you think joining StreamerPride Network might be right for you, feel free to get in contact with any of our &lt;a href=&quot;/StreamerPride/members&quot;&gt;founders&lt;/a&gt; directly through social media, DM our official &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/streamerpride&quot;&gt;@streamerpride Twitter&lt;/a&gt; account, or get in contact through the Contact page of this site. We strongly suggest you join our Discord community before applying so we can get to know you, and to have an active Twitch profile we can refer to and watch some of your VODs and join some of your upcoming live streams, to see if we feel you’d be a fit for us.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Our Website is LIVE]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to the official StreamerPride.Network website! This, along with our official twitter account @StreamerPride, is where we will be…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/website-is-live/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/website-is-live/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the official StreamerPride.Network website! This, along with our official twitter account &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/streamerpride&quot;&gt;@StreamerPride&lt;/a&gt;, is where we will be sharing all major news updates about our activities going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, feel free to take a look around and check out the profiles of our &lt;a href=&quot;/StreamerPride/members&quot;&gt;founding members&lt;/a&gt; as well as our &lt;a href=&quot;/StreamerPride/about&quot;&gt;mission statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to sharing many exciting things with you in the future!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>